We have the bladder and we have the insertion here at the
膀胱があり、ここにミュラー結節のレベル、尿生殖洞のレベルに挿入部があります。
Müllerian tubercle, at the urogenital sinus.
ミュラー結節のレベル、尿生殖洞のレベルに挿入部があります。
We have the portion here of the bladder, the urethra, and
ここに膀胱の部分、尿道があり、
then the attachment at the vagina.
そして膣への付着部があります。
This is mesoderm because it's from the Müllerian duct,
これは中胚葉です。なぜなら、これはミュラー管であり、
and it's from the vaginal plate through growth.
成長による膣の魂だからです。
The posterior growth of the sacrum and the neural tube, and
仙骨と神経管の後方成長と、
the differential growth rate compared to this part will create this opening space
この部分に対する分化成長速度が、膣のためのこの開口部空間を与えます。
for the vagina.
膣のためのこの開口部空間を与えます。
Again, it's the posterior part relative to my kidney, between the two, that creates this space
これは再び、私の腎臓に対する後方の部分であり、その間の部分が、その成長においてこの空間を作り出します。
in its growth.
その成長において。
With the Müllerian tubercle coming to sit here, an attachment is formed here.
ここにミュラー結節が来て、ここに付着部ができます。
The posterior differential growth, meaning the Müllerian tubercle...
後方の分化成長、つまりミュラー結節が...
Here, it will thicken, you see, it thickens, and then it will be as if
ここでは、それは厚くなります。見てください、それは厚くなり、そしてそれはまるで
stretched,
引き伸ばされるかのようですが、
but it's not that it's stretched, it's that the posterior part grows faster
しかし、それは引き伸ばされるのではなく、後方の部分がより速く成長しているのです。
and gives this kind of elongation, if you will, to finally form the vagina
そして、それがこの種の伸長を与え、最終的に膣を形成します。
which will be here
それはここにあり、
and the cervix, if you will.
そして子宮頸部も、もし望むなら。
So the posterior wall of the urogenital sinus will thicken here,
したがって、尿生殖洞の後壁はここで厚くなり、
and this will gradually form the vaginal plates here.
そしてそれは徐々にここに層を形成します。
vaginal plates that will open and stretch.
開いて伸びる膣の。
It's the same dynamic, but it's the posterior part
同じダイナミクスですが、ここでは後方の部分が
that will grow much faster here.
はるかに速く成長します。
It's both this and this that happens in relation to two movements.
これは、2つの動きに関して、これとこれが同時に起こっています。
This means that when we work on a uterus, I have the sacrum
つまり、子宮を治療するとき、私は仙骨を持ち、
and between the two, I have this kind of movement at the level of the peritoneum.
そしてその間に、腹膜のレベルでこの種の動きがあります。
What you're doing is very simple, but here,
あなたがしていることは非常に単純ですが、ここでは、
you have the meaning and the idea of what's happening.
何が起こっているのかの感覚とアイデアを持っています。
And it's in these two that I will have both the entire vaginal balance, the entire
そして、これら2つの中に、私は膣のすべてのバランス、子宮のすべてのバランスを持つことになります。
uterine balance.
子宮のバランス。
At the gonadal level, however, I do the opposite, I place myself at the level of the abdomen.
性腺のレベルでは、逆に、私は腹部に身を置きます。
It will be a movement where I will follow the ligament.
それは私が靭帯を追う動きになるでしょう。
And so, in fact, it's a movement like this towards the pubis.
そして実際、それはこのように恥骨に向かう動きです。
It's a wave that descends like this.
それはこのように下降する波です。
The descent of the sacrum through my neural tube.
私の神経管による仙骨の下降。
And here, I have another fulcrum.
そしてここには、もう一つの支点があります。
it's the combination, I'm exaggerating the movement, it's this.
それは組み合わせです。私は動きを誇張しています。それはこれです。
If I pull back, it's this.
もし私が引くなら、それはこれです。
This is a whole balance, from the pubis here,
これは、ここにある恥骨から始まる、全体のバランスです。
where I have the fascial balance at the level of the female lesser pelvis.
女性の骨盤内での顔面平衡がある場所です。
Here, I have another important point, don't forget.
そこには、もう一つ重要な点があります。忘れないでください。
The line is here, the line of force, like this.
線はここにあります、力線は、このように。
It's a relative downward movement compared to my sacrum.
それは私の仙骨に対して相対的な下降運動です。
The woman has frequently had miscarriages.
女性は頻繁に流産を経験しています。
It leaves a trace, because it was placed in the uterus.
それは痕跡を残します、なぜならそれは子宮に入れられたからです。
The uterus needs to be cleansed on an energetic level.
子宮をエネルギーレベルで浄化する必要があります。
When we take the uterus side, we can take it with a certain force
子宮側を取るとき、ある程度の力で取ることができます
at the magnetic level.
磁気レベルで。
You have to learn to feel.
感じることを学ぶ必要があります。
We stand slightly at a distance and we can gradually, until a given moment,
少し距離を置いて、少しずつ、ある時点まで、
You see, when I come here, there's a frequency that sets in and gradually,
ほら、私がここに来ると、そこに周波数が設定され、少しずつ、
she can even feel, there, she can start to feel a zone of warmth that will densify.
彼女は感じることさえできます、ほら、彼女は熱の領域を感じ始め、それが濃密になります。
I work like that, if necessary, and there I will scan, I will feel
私はこのように働きます、もし必要なら、そしてそこで私はスキャンし、感じます
if there are things that need to be cleaned or not, you see, that you can simply remove by speaking,
浄化する必要があるものがあるかどうか、ほら、言葉で簡単に取り除くことができるもの、
that you can guide, that you absolutely must give back freedom.
導くことができるもの、絶対に自由を取り戻さなければならないもの。
For example, I feel something that will express itself here, you see.
例えば、ここに表現される何かを感じます、ほら。
No, no, I'm on her electrical field.
いいえ、いいえ、私は彼女の電場にいます。
The normal uterus is here, and then this is a total retroversion,
通常の子宮はここにあり、そしてこれは後屈です
and you have different degrees.
完全なもので、様々な程度があります。
But knowing that this causes what are called congestive phases.
しかし、これがうっ血期と呼ばれるものを引き起こすことを知っておいてください。
The only thing I do is remote work,
私が唯一することは、遠隔で作業することです、
and I rebalance the gynecological system which is very important in relation to gastrin.
そして、ガストリンにとって非常に重要な婦人科系を再調整します。
There is also what is called endometriosis.
子宮内膜症と呼ばれるものもあります。
A proliferation that goes up into the peritoneum, this frequently causes significant lumbar
腹膜に広がる増殖は、頻繁に痛みを引き起こします
and sacroiliac pain.
重要な腰痛と仙腸関節痛。
In women, there is a direct link with, via the cervix,
女性には、子宮頸部を介して、卵管を介して、
via the fallopian tubes, with the intra-peritoneal cavity.
子宮頸部を介して、卵管を介して、腹腔内腔と直接的なつながりがあります。
This intra-peritoneal cavity is an important place, because it is the first cavity, it
この腹腔内腔は重要な場所です、なぜならそれは最初の腔であり、それは
is heaven.
天です。
Each state is there.
すべての状態はそこにあります。
best possible functional response. But depending on your life,
可能な限り最高の機能的応答。しかし、あなたの人生に応じて、
of your own life and the life
あなた自身の人生と
of your ancestors. You carry the best possible response at a given
あなたの祖先の。あなたは、ある瞬間に可能な限り最高の応答を運びます。
moment. And if it's necessary
そして、もし必要なら
for you to have a retroversion, perhaps it's the best response you have in relation to
あなたが後屈を持っているなら、それはあなたが解決しなければならない何かに対してあなたが持っている最高の応答かもしれません。
something you need to resolve. What you need to do is understand why you carry a transgenerational pattern
解決しなければならない何かに対して。必要なのは、なぜあなたが世代を超えたパターンを自分の中に持っているのかを理解することです。
within you, which has...
あなたの中に世代を超えたパターンを持っているのかを理解することです。
We are to have this best response.
私たちはこの最高の応答を持つことになっています。
Sometimes, it's necessary perhaps not to have children.
時には、子供を持たないことが必要かもしれません。
There's something too far back that hasn't been resolved, you see.
未解決のまま遠くにある何かがある、分かりますか。
So, it might be an answer, you see,
だから、それは一つの答えかもしれないし、
or it might be another more subtle answer.
あるいはもっと微妙な別の答えかもしれません。
It's always the best possibility we'll find in its response.
それは常に、その答えの中に見出される最善の可能性です。
And it's up to us to have the right decoding and the right formulation,
そして、適切な解読と適切な表現を持つのは私たち次第です。
if necessary, if requested, to be able to provide the release.
必要であれば、求められれば、解放を与えることができます。
because people come looking for the point where they can be freed.
なぜなら、人々は解放される場所を求めてやってくるからです。
You have people who come, if you don't recognize it, you might see it once, then they'll leave.
もしあなたがそれを認識しなければ、一度は来るかもしれませんが、その後は去ってしまうでしょう。
The embryo shows us that at each stage of development, it always has the best
胚は、発生の各段階において、常に最善の
physiological response in its development.
生理学的応答をその発生の中に持っていることを示しています。
The neural tube here, and behind it, there's what's called a caudal eminence.
管はここで不平を言わず、その後ろには尾部隆起と呼ばれるものがあります。
There will be like a lumen, a space that will open.
光のようなもの、空間が開くでしょう。
And connection, we see the caudal bud, the terminal part of
そして接続、私たちは尾芽、つまり
the notochord.
脊索の終端部分を見ます。
I have the space of the rectum and then I have the neural tube here, you see, with the posterior neuropore.
直腸の空間があり、ここに神経管があり、後部神経孔があります。
Well, there will be a connection that will be made in relation to all this developmental movement
そして、この発生運動全体に関して接続が形成されます。
which is much more important in the posterior part than in the anterior part.
それは前部よりも後部の方がはるかに重要です。
With the closure here and a reopening here to provide this connection.
ここで閉鎖し、ここで再開してこの接続を与えます。
And that's how we're going to end up with a speed, with a fulcrum that we're going to call here
そして、このようにして、私たちは速度と、ここで呼ぶところの支点を持つことになります。
the emergence of my posterior neuropore which is here,
ここにある私の後部神経孔の出現、
and then the elongation to form my filum terminale.
そして私の終糸を形成するための伸長です。
And this will form what we call secondary neurulation.
そして、これは二次神経管形成と呼ばれるものを形成します。
When I take the sacrum in hand, it gives you new information.
仙骨を手に取ると、新しい情報が得られます。
We see again that these are differential growth rates, you see, with the fulcrum right here
成長速度が異なることが再び分かります。私の仙骨に対して、支点がちょうどここにあるのです。
in relation to my sacrum.
私の仙骨に対して。
that develops. Initially,
発達している。最初は、
this junction here
ここのこの接合部は
is already there. And then it's a posterior
すでに存在しています。そして、それは伸長です。
elongation with the integration
この隆起の統合を伴う後方への伸長です。
of this caudal
この隆起の
eminence to form the
尾部を形成し、
continuity with the neural tube
神経管との連続性を形成し、
and form what we call
そして、私たちが呼ぶところの
this ascending secondary neurulation.
この二次的な上行性神経管形成を形成します。
At the perineum,
会陰部では、
I will have here
ここに
the emergence
私の手足の
of my limbs.
出現があります。
inferior and I have a traction that occurs here, this movement with
下肢と、ここで子宮系と傾きを伴うこの動きによって牽引が起こります。
the uterine system and the tilting
子宮系と傾き
of the liver here in relation to that movement brings, you see, with the descent here
肝臓が、この動きによって、ほら、ここでの下降とともに引き戻される
of my
私の
neural tube, the sacrum, the movement here of development that will
神経管、仙骨、ここでの発生の動きが
pull towards the white
白線に向かって引っ張られる
line with the falciform ligament, you see, which pulls, it will give and
鎌状靭帯によって、ほら、それが引っ張られることで、それが与えられ、
it's development
そして、それは発達である
hepatis that happens like this
このようにして形成される肝臓の
like this, you see, will bring this tilting and bring
このようにして、ほら、この傾きが引き起こされ、そして
the entire uterine zone that develops this way, through here,
この経路、ここを通って発達する子宮全体が引き戻される
and which could perhaps explain phenomena of migration, of differential traction
そして、それはおそらく、肝臓系に対する移動現象、牽引現象を説明できるかもしれない
in relation to the hepatic system,
異なる牽引現象を、
in relation to the uterine position.
子宮の位置に関して。
There is a kind of ligament that develops here, between
恥骨と臍の間には、ここに一種の靭帯が発達している。
the pubis and the umbilicus.
恥骨と臍の間。
contains the entire history of your descent and your uterine formation,
あなたの下降と子宮形成の全歴史を含んでいる
concentration in the tissue
組織内の集中
of that, just as the sternum also contains a history of your flexion there,
それの、胸骨があなたの屈曲の歴史もそこに含まれているように
that contains a history of your entire
それは、あなたの
posterior formation and the gonadization and uterinization of the pelvis, the
後方形成と生殖腺形成、そして骨盤の子宮化の全歴史を含んでいる
ventral ligament
腹側靭帯
medial here on the white line, and this white line is precisely the
白線上の内側、そしてこの白線はまさに
reunion of all
すべての結合である
urogenital.
性器の。